今早的训练太棒了  獠牙
Great training sesh this morning, fangs.
赶鸭子实在是太好玩了
It was so much fun chasing ducks.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
它们真是身在福中不知福
They've had it too good for too long.
我觉得午餐有肉下肚了
I think we've earned lunch.
怎么在地板上吃东西
Eating off the floor.
你们是给狼养大的么
Were you raised by wolves?
妈
Mom.
噢  抱歉抱歉
Oh, sorry sorry.
真是太对不起了
Sorry sorry sorry.
獠牙  你能这么辛苦地训练我真是谢谢了
Thanks for training with me so hard this week, fangs.
我这次试镜胜券在握了
I am going to nail this audition.
我拿定了这个角色  对不对
That part is so mine, am I right?
当一只狼很安静  就说明它不同意我的看法
When the wolf is silent, the wolf disapproves.
到底怎么了
What's wrong?
就你现在的表现而言  唯一能搞定试镜的方式
As good as you're doing, the only way you're gonna nail that audition
就是搞定你的嚎叫声
is if you nail your howl.
这是每一只狼的内心和灵魂所在
It is the heart and soul of any wolf.
呃  我
Wow, I...
觉得你好像吓着所有邻居家的狗狗了
Think you scared every dog in the neighborhood.
不
No.
隔壁街区有只杜宾狗没回复我
There's a doberman on the next block who didn't reply.
这下他回复了
There he is.
他是在道歉
He apologized.
你总不能一边撒尿一边嚎叫吧
You can't pee and bark at the same time.
好了  鲁尼  到你了
Okay, Rooney. Your turn.
好的
Okay.
(曲调是福音歌曲《奇异恩典》)
别再不务正业了
Quit goofing around.
你嚎叫的时候一点都不认真
You're not taking your howl seriously.
跟你说吧
You know what?
我不干了
I'm out.
什么
What?
你不能不干啊  我们是一伙的
You can't be out. We're in a pack.
你还舔过我的脸呢
You licked my face.
抱歉了  鲁尼
I'm sorry, Rooney.
我们已经尽力了
We've gone as far as we can go.
还有就是我总痒痒  但你妈不给我在你们家地毯上挠屁股
Plus, I'm itchy and your mom won't let me drag my butt on your carpet.
你猜怎么着 好吧
You know what? Fine.
我会在没有你的帮助的情况下  成为一个了不起的特里斯坦的
I am going to be an awesome Tristan without your help.
哦  你想吃这块肉么
Oh, you want this?
唔  很好
Mmm. Yeah?
我知道你早就垂涎三尺了
Yeah, I know you want it.
香喷喷的  对不
Yum yum, right?
快去拿吧
Go get it!
真是只笨狼啊
Stupid wolf.